Wow, this is old K. What follows is one of the most gimmicky events in the history of Operation Delta.
He was mentioned during the S5 preview live broadcast, and was mentioned again in the mid-season update.
Even the Treasure Rat Mouse event last week was still setting the stage for him.
Even the Delta Pass signature has become this, ah, Treasure Month event. It is conceivable that
How great this event will be. Let’s move on to the event. First, we will give away a legendary weapon bundle.
And it’s still two out of three. Yes, that's the picture.
Everyone should be able to tell what kind of gun this is, right? It doesn’t matter if you don’t see it, I’ll list it for you.
Order French fries on the hour, A fights K four or M four, and then kills the Tesla coil,
M P seven S R three M S twelve K Hunting time G three M sixteen Victor.
The choice of gun this time is pretty good, and the skin of this gun has been revealed a long time ago.
Let’s take a look at the video made by this UP owner.
The S5 Hunting Time series includes the M Yaoliu S assault rifle, Victor submachine gun and G3 combat rifle.
The skin's appearance is made from a variety of animal bones.